# ASHLEE GUDEMAN

Ashleegudeman@gmail.com · (407) 459-2454 https://github.com/agudeman

As a highly creative and detail-oriented web designer with 2 years of experience, I specialize in developing visually appealing and user-friendly websites. With a strong grasp of HTML/CSS and JavaScript, I am well-versed in responsive design and UI/UX principles. My passion for staying up to date with the latest design trends and technologies allows me to create engaging online experiences that captivate audiences.

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- Procreate
- Attention to detail

- Vectornator
- Web design and development
- Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint
- Excellent team player

## **EDUCATION**

**JULY 2024** 

## WEB DEVELOPMENT, VALENCIA COLLEGE (AUGUST 2022 - PRESENT)

- Expected Graduation Date: July 2024
- RELEVANT COURSE WORK: Web Essentials, Introduction to Web Programming

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### ATTRACTIONS OPERATIONS, UNIVERSAL STUDIOS ORLANDO (2014 - PRESENT)

Head of Guest Service Committee, Transformers: The Ride 3D

• Managed guest flow while ensuring safety concerns and guest satisfaction.

#### **COPORATE TRAINER, DUFFYS SPORTS GRILL (2005 – 2014)**

Corporate Trainer, Promotions Team

 Worked for the promotions team as a corporate trainer to help new locations train and operate smoothly while ensuring guest satisfaction.

#### STAGECRAFT VOLUNTEER, ST. LUCIE WEST CENTENNIAL HIGH SCHOOL (2005-2007)

Les Miserables, Peter Pan, You're A Good Man Charlie Brown

Worked with team to build sets for multiple school plays

#### RECOGNITION

**GUEST SERVICE AWARD, UNIVERSAL STUDIOS FLORIDA (2022)** 

ACADEMIC ACHEIVEMENT AWARD, ST. LUCIE WEST CENTENNIAL HIGH SCHOOL (2007)